So let's say now we're at a speaking event.
所以让我们说现在我们正在参加一个演讲活动。
We've gone to an event where there will be a speaker talking about some topic or maybe there will be
我们参加了一个活动，那里会有演讲者谈论某个话题，或者可能会有
several speakers or perhaps it's a conference.
几位演讲者，或者可能是一次会议。
Several days several speakers a lot of different meetings things like that.
几天几个演讲者很多不同的会议都是这样的。
OK so someone's going to give a talk and it's a well-known person let's say his name is Francis Kane.
好的，所以有人要发表演讲，这是一个众所周知的人，假设他的名字是弗朗西斯凯恩。
I'm making this up.
我正在编造这个。
All right.
好的。
So friends Cain is going to give a talk.
所以朋友该隐要发表演讲。
If your name is Francis Cain.
如果你的名字是弗朗西斯凯恩。
That is insane.
那太疯狂了。
You must have communicated to me in the past.
你以前一定和我交流过。
So how do you know the speaker if this were hanging out maybe before the talk hanging out before this
那么你怎么知道演讲者是否在这之前的谈话之前挂出
person's presentation.
人的介绍。
Maybe I'll have a beer or maybe it's this kind of relaxed event.
也许我会喝杯啤酒，或者这是一种轻松的活动。
I've got a beer.
我有啤酒。
This could be called a mixer.
这可以称为混合器。
Sometimes there are mixers where you have a presentation and also the opportunity to mix with other
有时有混音器，您可以在其中进行演示，也有机会与其他人混音
people.
人们。
Well that's the perfect opportunity to start conversations.
嗯，这是开始对话的绝佳机会。
That's kind of what mixers are for.
这就是混音器的用途。
Right.
正确的。
OK.
好的。
So how do you know the speaker.
那你怎么知道说话的人。
Actually I worked with him several years ago.
事实上，几年前我和他一起工作过。
He was my boss.
他是我的老板。
So the speaker maybe is fairly well-known person.
所以演讲者可能是相当知名的人。
Now we have a lot to talk about.
现在我们有很多话要说。
Or actually I watched a couple of his lectures on YouTube.
或者实际上我在 YouTube 上看过他的一些讲座。
So I wanted to come to see him speak.
所以我想来看他讲话。
How do you know the speaker.
你怎么知道说话的人。
Actually I'm not familiar with the speaker.
其实我对喇叭并不熟悉。
What's he going to talk about.
他要谈什么。
I'm just here for the mixer.
我只是来调音台的。
So doesn't matter what the answer is even if they don't know the speaker then they can say something
所以不管答案是什么，即使他们不认识说话者，他们也可以说些什么
else that you can grab on to.
否则你可以抓住。
I'm just here for the mixer than I can say Oh actually the speaker is going to be talking about or I
我只是为调音台而来
could maybe ask some other question about why they wanted to come here for the mixer.
也许可以问一些其他问题，关于他们为什么想来这里参加调音台。
I could say Oh so what company are you with.
我可以说哦，那你在哪家公司。
Right.
正确的。
My follow up question What company are you with.
我的后续问题你在哪家公司。
Then people can talk about the company that they represent or if they don't represent a company and
然后人们可以谈论他们所代表的公司，或者如果他们不代表公司，并且
they're there by themselves.
他们自己在那里。
Well that's also interesting.
嗯，这也很有趣。
So again it's not too important what question it is.
所以同样，它是什么问题并不重要。
As long as it's related to the situation or contextual and hopefully a little bit interesting.
只要它与情况或上下文相关，并希望有点有趣。
Again the goal of the question should be to get the other person to want to say something they shouldn't
同样，问题的目标应该是让对方想说他们不应该说的话
have to struggle to say something.
不得不挣扎着说些什么。
Now we could also make comments.
现在我们也可以发表评论了。
I like your hat.
我喜欢你的帽子。
Did you make that.
你做到了吗。
This is a question and a comment.
这是一个问题和一个评论。
Maybe someone is wearing a I don't know a really cool fedora.
也许有人戴着我不知道的非常酷的软呢帽。
Maybe they're wearing a fedora.
也许他们戴着软呢帽。
And you don't usually see a person wearing a fedora at conference.
而且你通常不会在会议上看到有人戴着软呢帽。
So you say I like your hat.
所以你说我喜欢你的帽子。
Very simple.
很简单。
Did you make it.
你做了吗。
Maybe it looks kind of messy.
也许它看起来有点乱。
Then they probably want to talk about it.
然后他们可能想谈论它。
If somebody is going to wear something that's a little different than everybody else wearing a hat at
如果有人要穿的东西与其他人戴帽子的东西有点不同
a conference they might want to talk about it.
他们可能想谈论它的会议。
I realize that question seems a little silly but it's something and at least I can see if that person
我意识到这个问题似乎有点傻，但它是一些东西，至少我可以看到那个人n
wants to have a conversation or not.
想不想谈。
And it is showing interest in them.
它对他们表现出兴趣。
It's showing that hey I noticed something about you.
这表明嘿，我注意到了你的一些事情。
It could even be somebodies shoes or the way that somebody is standing maybe they're standing by themselves.
甚至可能是某人的鞋子或某人站立的方式，也许他们独自站立。
And I could say hey we why are you standing by yourself.
我可以说，嘿，我们为什么你一个人站着。
This is a mixer.
这是一个搅拌机。
Right.
正确的。
And then they could say Oh well I you know I'm just not really in a good mood or whatever.
然后他们可以说哦，好吧，我知道我只是心情不太好或其他什么。
Again notice something.
再次注意到一些东西。
Notice something about them.
注意他们的一些事情。
Don't make it all about you.
不要把一切都与你有关。
Make it about them.
关于他们。
Make a comment about them.
对他们发表评论。
Make a comment about the situation that you share and then you can judge to see if they would like to
对您分享的情况发表评论，然后您可以判断他们是否愿意
talk to you or not.
和你谈谈与否。
This one is just a regular comment that we could make about the situation not about you not about me.
这只是一个常规的评论，我们可以对这种情况发表评论，而不是关于你，也不是关于我。
I'm surprised so many people showed up here on a Tuesday or maybe it's Tuesday afternoon and you expect
我很惊讶有这么多人在周二或周二下午出现在这里，你期待
people to be at work or at school.
人们在工作或在学校。
And so it's kind of unexpected that this place would be so busy so full this event but maybe the speaker
所以有点出乎意料的是这个地方会这么忙这么满这个活动但也许是演讲者
is very popular.
很受欢迎。
So the other person could say well you know the speaker is very popular.
所以对方可能会说你知道演讲者很受欢迎。
He's got a lot of fans on YouTube.
他在 YouTube 上有很多粉丝。
So makes sense to me.
所以对我来说很有意义。
Yeah.
是的。
I didn't actually know he had so many fans on YouTube.
我真的不知道他在 YouTube 上有这么多粉丝。
Actually I haven't seen any of his YouTube videos.
实际上，我还没有看过他的任何 YouTube 视频。
Really.
真的。
You should really watch them because he's got some really great videos whatever you want to say the
你真的应该看他们，因为无论你想说什么，他都有一些非常棒的视频
conversation then can continue from there.
然后可以从那里继续对话。
You may notice that at no point have I said my name is Luke.
你可能会注意到，我从来没有说过我的名字是卢克。
Hello.
你好。
Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
My name is Luke.
我叫卢克。
Usually you shouldn't begin a conversation this way if you walk up to someone who you don't know and
通常，如果你走到一个你不认识的人面前，你不应该以这种方式开始谈话
you say hello there.
你在那里打招呼。
My name is Luke.
我叫卢克。
It's odd it's awkward it's strange.
很奇怪很尴尬很奇怪。
So when should you say it when should you say your name when should you introduce yourself.
所以你什么时候应该说，什么时候应该说你的名字，什么时候你应该介绍自己。
That can be very quick and it's not really a big deal.
这可能非常快，而且没什么大不了的。
Maybe you make a comment or ask a simple question as we've been talking about.
正如我们一直在谈论的那样，也许您发表评论或提出一个简单的问题。
And then at some point after a minute or two into the conversation you say by the way by the way I'm
然后在谈话一两分钟后的某个时候，你说的顺便说一句，我是
Luke.
卢克。
And if you just say that they'll probably say Oh and I'm Kathy.
如果你只是说他们可能会说哦，我是凯西。
Whatever the other person's name is you could say what's your name.
不管对方叫什么名字，你都可以说出你的名字。
But if you start with that.
但如果你从那个开始。
It's quite awkward.
这很尴尬。
And then it's hard to get a conversation going from there.
然后很难从那里开始对话。
Now you could use very general questions like What company do you represent.
现在您可以使用非常笼统的问题，例如您代表哪家公司。
But my recommendation is to first think what you have in common and then come up with the good common.
但我的建议是首先考虑你的共同点，然后提出好的共同点。
Good question.
好问题。
Then everything else should be pretty easy.
那么其他一切都应该很容易。
The conversation should flow.
对话应该流畅。
And after a while you can say by the way my name is Luke.
过了一会儿，你可以顺便说一下我的名字是卢克。
So that's pretty easy right.
所以这很容易。
So we've learned the techniques for getting conversations started with people that we don't know we
所以我们已经学会了与我们不认识的人开始对话的技巧
need to look at the situation itself.
需要看情况本身。
Think about what we share with others.
想想我们与他人分享的内容。
Ask good questions.
问好问题。
Make interesting comments.
发表有趣的评论。
Pay attention to body language.
注意肢体语言。
To practice this.
要练习这个。
What I'd like you to do is look at this situation.
我希望你做的是看看这种情况。
The first day of work.
第一天上班。
It's kind of similar to the first day of school one and come up with three to five questions that would
这有点类似于上学的第一天，提出三到五个问题
be good to ask somebody in this situation.
在这种情况下最好问别人。
Maybe it's not their first day of work.
也许这不是他们上班的第一天。
It's just your first day of work so you might be talking to somebody who's been working here for a while.
这只是你工作的第一天，所以你可能正在和在这里工作了一段时间的人交谈。
Be a new person in the office.
成为办公室里的新人。
OK three to five questions and then ask yourself the questions or ask somebody else the questions a
确定三到五个问题，然后问自己问题或问别人问题
friend and practice and see if these questions help get the conversation started.
朋友和练习，看看这些问题是否有助于开始对话。
Again the questions should be contextual should be interesting and should make the other person want
同样，问题应该与上下文相关，应该很有趣，并且应该让其他人想要
to say something back.
回话。
Want to explain themselves.
想自己解释。
Want to talk about something.
想谈点什么。
This is the key to having natural conversations with people you just met.
这是与刚认识的人进行自然对话的关键。
Good luck.
祝你好运。